

# Lasse Lund-Egmose

Curriculum Vitae

#### Contact

☑ lasse@lle.engineer

+45 23 90 21 19

🤛 lle.engineer

in /Lasse-Lund-Egmose

### Interests

- Engineering
- · Cybersecurity
- · Ethical Hacking
- · Cryptography
- · Embedded Systems & IoT
- · Operating Systems (kernels)
- Project Planning & Mgmt

## Passion for technological engineering

Ever since I at an early age experienced the feeling of creating something that is comprehensible by a computer, I have known that I have a great interest in technology. Since then, I've worked hard to continuously broaden my skill set. Having started out with a focus on development of websites and more involved web solutions, I have in the recent years found a great interest in the further complex technological areas of cybersecurity and embedded systems. Currently, I am studying a master's degree in Computer Science & Engineering at Technical University of Denmark (DTU), which, in combination with my bachelor's degree in Software Technology, will result in a Civil Engineering degree (cand.polyt) in 2024.

# Work experience

#### **Teaching Assistant — DTU**

Kongens Lyngby, 2022

For the exercise sessions of the DTU Course "Introduction to Software Technology", I was hired to support the learning process of the students taking the course during exercise sessions.

#### **Backend Developer** — Morningscore

Remote, 2019-2021

Hired to develop parts of the Morningscore application remotely, where I worked on major projects, I had a great amount of responsibility, and I had to meet my deadlines — and did. I primarily dealt with the complex task of integrating towards other systems such as the payment gateway (Stripe) or the CRM system (HubSpot).

#### **Backend Developer / Project Manager — Morning Train**

Odense C, 2018-2019

Full-time programming and project management job at a web agency, where I made websites tailored to the needs of our customers. I underwent a sales training program by "SalgsPiloterne".

## **Education**

MSc. in Computer Science & Engineering – Technical University of Denmark Kongens Lyngby, 2022-now I am currently studying a master's degree in Computer Science & Engineering at Technical University of Denmark (DTU) towards a Civil Engineering (cand.polyt) degree. My courses align with the Computer Security study line. I expect to graduate in the summer of 2024.

#### BSc. in Software Technology – Technical University of Denmark

Kongens Lyngby, 2019-2022

I followed a wide variety of courses to learn the central aspect of software engineering. I also studied abroad at University of Leeds in the fall of 2021.

#### High school - Sct. Knuds Gymnasium

Odense M, 2015-2018

Focus on natural sciences. Member of The Academy for Talented Youth (ATU). Hired by Sct. Knuds Gymnasium to work as tutor in my final year.







